Thunder buddies for life.
Ted 2 is a comedy, fantasy film directed by Seth MacFarlane.
Newlywed couple Ted and Tami-Lynn want to have a baby, but in order to qualify to be
a parent, Ted will have to prove he's a person in a court of law.
John, played by Mark Wahlberg.
Ted (voice), played by Seth MacFarlane.
Samantha, played by Amanda Seyfried.
Tami-Lynn, played by Jessica Barth.
Donny, played by Giovanni Ribisi.
Patrick Meighan, played by Morgan Freeman.
Ted 2 (stylized as ted2) is a 2015 American fantasy comedy film, directed by Seth
MacFarlane, and written by MacFarlane, Alec Sulkin and Wellesley Wild.
Mark Wahlberg, MacFarlane, Giovanni Ribisi, and Jessica Barth reprise their roles from the first
film, with Amanda Seyfried, John Slattery, and Morgan Freeman joining the cast.
The film follows talking teddy bear Ted as he fights for his civil rights in order to
be recognized as a person and not as property so he can adopt a child.
Principal photography began in Massachusetts in July 2014.
Ted 2 was released in the United States on June 26, 2015, by Universal Pictures.
It received mixed reviews from critics, and was a box office
success, grossing $216 million on a $68 million budget.
It was followed by a prequel television series, which premiered in 2024.
The film explores themes of sperm bank, sequel, buddy, courthouse, teddy bear.
The tone is lighthearted.